Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's really
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the waves.
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
What in the world has
happened to our beloved king?
The whole kingdom's in disarray!
He looked amiss when he
left the palace earlier,
but there's no way anyone could
have predicted something like this.
I fear this is more than
we can handle on our own.
I have already called
for naval assistance.
Captain Vergo has stated
he's mobilizing in response.
Oh, splendid idea.
Oh, father.
Monnet!
What's going on?
What are you doing in here?
You're just a servant.
Why are you manning the palace gates?
Princess Viola.
I'm sure you're confused
about what's happening.
Perhaps you should use your
clairvoyance to get a closer look.
You might be surprised by what you see.
And while you're here, why don't you
welcome our new royal family to the throne?
The East Tower's been hit!
Pirates have reached the palace grounds!
They've taken Princess Viola hostage!
This place is bigger than I expected.
Not too shabby. Yeah!
I can get used to this!
The young master will love this place!
It's got everything!
Hold, intruders!
Are you Doflamingo's men? Monet!
Let go of the princess at once!
Are you responsible for
King Riku's behavior?
Move along!
We've got a busy day ahead of us!
Let's start with cleaning
up the palace grounds!
What are you attacking us?
King Rick!
Please, I beg you, stop!
If there's no way to prevent
me from hurting my own people.
Then I'd rather be dead.
Someone, anyone, please kill me!
Why, King Rick?
Have we done something wrong?
I don't understand.
How did it come to this?
You were always a fair
and just king to us.
You told us that you
needed all of our money.
And we brought you everything we had.
We trusted you.
Because you always put your people first.
No matter what.
You were our pride and joy.
King Rick, I can't believe you've
forsaken your kingdom like that.
How could you?
He took our money and he
slaughtered our people.
He tossed us aside to
satisfy his own desires.
King Rick, you monster.
I hate you.
You're...
You're nothing but a
low-down dirty scumbag!
Here comes the king's army! Hurry!
Get out of there! Run!
No! Help!
Who are you people?
We have come to rescue
this broken kingdom.
So say hello to your new
ruler, Don Quixote do Flamingo.
Those are pirates.
They're saving us from the royal army.
But why?
Are you enjoying this dance, King Rick?
Who is that guy? Who's that guy?
Treble Pika.
Diamante.
Come out, it's go time.
Now, get out there and cleanse
this country of its trash.
He's a hero.
We somehow survived. Yeah!
Doflamingo!
Look at that.
They embrace violence easily.
In just a single night, the kingdom fell.
Into the vile hands of Doflamingo.
That's a terrible story.
Oh, man, what a nightmare.
How utterly ruthless.
I already hate that Doflamingo guy.
Regrettably, we fell for it, too.
Thinking that King Rick had lost his mind,
we reached out to the new king and were
duped into our current circumstances.
I'm so ashamed of myself
forever trusting him.
So sad.
That's a real shame.
It must be so frustrating to
know that the once-beloved king
of this country was set up and
tragically died a hated man.
Not quite, for King Rick is still alive.
Princess Viola had an ability that
Doflamingo was particularly drawn to.
So she made a bargain with him.
If you promise to let my father
live, then I'll submit to you.
Please, anything!
Just spare him!
Still to this day, she works
under Doflamingo's command.
Only now she is known as Violet,
one of the family officers.
She's an officer then.
King Rick is still alive,
thanks to her plea deal.
That's right.
He's still out there somewhere,
perhaps in this kingdom,
even but I cannot imagine the anguish
he's carried with him these past 10 years,
nor how hard this must be on the
former princess: fear, anger, tears.
I wonder how she has fared
over this past decade.
There is also the lasting pain the
soldiers have endured this whole time.
Just like King Rick,
they were forced against their will into
violent acts against their fellow citizens.
You mean Doflamingo?
Didn't finish off the
royal soldiers that night?
Some soldiers surrendered
to Doflamingo while
others weren't so lucky
and were slain into chaos.
The known survivors are currently
serving as guards for him.
Get for nothing, sellouts perhaps,
so but I believe it must have been an
agonizing decision for them, murderers.
They were only following
orders of a deranged King.
Forgive them, and I will put these
blindly loyal soldiers to good use.
Oh man, this story's chock
full of betrayal, suffering.
These tears are rusting me, bro.
While a good number surrendered,
many men lost their lives that day,
but even when you add up those numbers,
it doesn't account for
a kingdom's full army.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
It sounds strange, but it
seems I've lost some memories.
Others have too, and how
does that work exactly?
I have a theory, Fralin, do you?
You recall what I told you before?
When we are turned into toys, we retain
all our memories from when we were human.
But people around us,
including our families,
lose theirs and forget we
even existed in their lives.
What the heck?
They're completely unaware
they've lost a loved one.
Even we toys can forget
some details as well.
This is the most heartbreaking
tragedy Desrosa faces. You mean,
it's possible that even some of the
toys walking around town may have
forgotten about their friends and family
and that could include you as well,
precisely but I do believe even
with their muddled minds that
everyone turned into a toy must
feel vengeful towards Doflamingo.
Doflamingo attempted to
bury the will of the people,
but that naturally only fueled
the rage and insurgency dwelling
within the shadows of this
kingdom they long for revolution.
The key to our victory
lies with them—that unknown
quantity of downtrodden
and silenced individuals.
individuals I'm on the same page now!
So you're counting on that advantage
to win this thing, then, huh?
While the folks gathered
here may not be enough
manpower to take on a
warlord and his lackeys,
you're betting that if you can recruit
all the downtrodden toys to join you,
it'll give you that extra edge!
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait!
Are you seriously getting yourself
pumped up to take down Doflamingo, too?!
Our only objective here is
to destroy the damn factory!
We're ditching this place
once it's mission complete!
Back me up, Robin!
I'll crush you, Doflamingo.
Yeah! What she said!
WHAAAAH!
Today will go down as
the day of reckoning!
This morning's incident was
a challenge from our enemies!
It's no mere coincidence that
brave Oceland came to us today!
Divine Intervention is
telling us to fight! Yeah!
What incident again?
The flamingo's brief
abdication from the throne.
Oh, that.
Well, you see, uh...
Can you imagine the joy we felt
when we heard word of the news?
We thought it was a miracle.
However,
when we found it was a false report,
we felt as if we had dropped
from the edge of heaven.
into the boiling pits of hell.
And yet, instead of being
trapped in our despair,
we decided to take the final stand today!
Oh, crap!
That's on us, isn't it?
Regrettably, I've yet to find a
successor to the Haposui army.
If only I had a grandson to take my place,
unfortunate—it's not
easy being a pirate, huh?
Perhaps
it's just my imagination,
but I feel like I'm forgetting something I
experienced a phenomenon
like this about 10 years ago.
Hey, hey, hey, where am I going, grandpa?
Please, you gotta help.
Oh no—what have they done
to Abdullah the lone wolf?
What have they done to me?
Cheat the maverick!
the maverick
Warrior! Help!
Zoro!
That stupid roosterhead guy.
He told me he was going to show me
the way, but then he passed out.
Is Zoro even here?
Hey!
Zoro!
Yo, keep him on!
I'm up here, you guys! Luffy!
Shh!
Stop yelling so loud, would you?
So you met with the green-haired man.
I was somewhat reticent
about trusting him at first,
but he seemed quite eager to
offer his assistance to us.
Where is he now?
I don't know.
He just, like, passed out or something.
Passed out?
What is wrong with that guy? Beats me.
There you are, Straw Hat.
Finally.
So Joker is ordering me
to murder Straw Hat now?
Make sure it's done before
the competition ends.
You do want to become an executive
of the family, don't you?
Nothing personal.
This is just the way it is.
I don't know, maybe
he's sick or something.
He was acting real weird.
Whatever.
Something happened? Hey!
Nah, nothing.
Anyway, it's like a
maze in here, you guys.
I keep getting lost.
There you are Bellamy, so
have you murdered him yet?
I bet you haven't you big dummy.
Huh?
Challenger? I'm busy.
Well,
if you're standing there
and not murdering Straw Hat,
then I say you're not busy enough.
You need me to give you a hand?
Puss off.
He's a lot stronger than you.
We expected you'd screw it up.
But, you know, it doesn't
matter if you fail.
In fact, the whole thing never
mattered in the first place.
What do you mean?
The assassination order was mostly just
an attempt to get you out of the way.
It's annoying how you keep trying
to win our approval, you know.
That's why I'm going to finish
you off right here and now.
On the Young Master's order.
No, that can't be. Oops!
I shouldn't have said
that part out loud, huh?
Sorry!
He wants me dead?
Scalpel!
You can't escape me, rat!
And shovels!
What the hell?
That opiopi fruit of yours is handy.
Though I did notice, there seems to be a
limit to how much you can use its power.
How much more have you got, huh?
Bullet string.
So, now what? Law.
So close.
Tres Rosas right there.
Oh, sorry.
Are you in the middle of
some business right now?
No, it's nothing. Go ahead.
Violet betrayed us, and
she's making a run for it.
Seeing as Blackleg is still alive, I
suppose I should have expected as much.
So,
needless to say,
we weren't able to use
her glare glare power
to figure out what the
Straw Hats were up to.
Still in the dark on that, I'm afraid.
Don't worry, it's all under control.
So here's the deal: I need you to deploy.
Loud, you and the others to the
entrance of the Smile Factory!
Whoa, whoa—no, can do.
We've already announced that those guys
will be participating in the finals the.
Crowds gonna be angry—stop!
You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
Exactly what you are, my friend—no, no!
I'm nothing of a sort honestly.
The only one who can do
this fine—I'm a genius.
You can count on me, galik.
What are you doing with me?
Is that a problem?
You're trying to act as a decoy
to keep me busy. Aren't you?
And in the meantime,
the Straw Hats are planning to destroy
my factory—even if you die here!
As long as the factory's destroyed,
your plan succeeds
because Kaido will kill me
when I can no longer
produce smiles for him.
That's how your scenario goes, isn't it?
But you used up your power too quickly
and hardly bought any time at all.
If the Straw Hats can't seem
to pull it together—either
you went on about how you
were just using them—but if
you didn't have the utmost
faith in Straw Hat and his
crew then the plan would
never work in the first place.
So.
never work in the first place so
But where does that come from?
Why do you trust that kid?
Because I know that the
D will bring a new storm.
So, what did you need me for, Zoro?
First off, there's a tournament
going on and you didn't even tell me.
I want to fight too, you know.
Oops, sorry.
I can't believe you're letting
that old man kick your ass.
What were you doing?
I beat him in the end.
That's him.
No mistaking it.
Vice Admiral Bastille!
As I thought, that was Pirate
Hunter Zoro back there.
And the guy in the
Coliseum he's talking to?
I'm almost positive
that's Straw Hat Luffy.
So he was the winner from Block C?
Lucy, right?
Well, that explains why he was so strong.
Then it looks like Smoker had it right.
The Straw Hats are in Dressrosa.
Should we capture them?
No, let's leave them be for now.
Think about it for a second as we speak,
that coliseum is swimming
with infamous pirates,
deadly bounty hunters and mercenaries
from all over the new world?
Sure, we could burst in
there and capture Straw Hat,
but that would make a scene we
don't want to alert the others yet?
If we wait for all of those snakes to
slither their way out of the coliseum,
they'll fall right into our trap,
then we can capture the lot
of them in one fell swoop.
Well, let's see.
who's been eliminated.
Biggest is Don Chinjou.
Then there's Usai, Boo, and Abdullah?
Wait a sec.
Who were we supposed to capture again?
Hmm.
Am I using this snail correctly?
What are you trying to do?
Sir Sanji requested that
I call him once we found Sir Luffy. I see.
Oh, and Luffy?
The Coliseum is surrounded
by marines by the
way that was our big news
and you don't even care
the transponder snail is ringing
must be kinemo if that's the
case then please allow me to answer
this is the sunny here hey it's
me hi lucy all right chopper now
call us off on the other one this
is everybody we're missing law
but he can catch up with the news
later i'm give us a status update
please we made
some friends guys
they call themselves the King Rick
army sworn enemies of Doflamingo
an army of little people it's a hero
meeting
a
top You remember
that toy soldier dude we met in
front of the Coliseum earlier?
Uh-huh, but about the little people.
Turns out that toy is the
commander of this here army.
Of the little people? Yeah.
And the thing is, this army is planning
on taking down Doflamingo, like, pronto.
Today, even.
Hold on.
I believe that he can save this kingdom,
but he wants to sacrifice
his life to do it.
Hey, I heard something about that soldier.
Earlier, Rebecca said she
wants to stop him. Don't do it.
Tell the army to wait.
Not a chance.
We need to do the exact opposite of that.
So, wait, you said you talked to Rebecca?
Yeah, and she's really nice,
so I want to help her out.
Even though she's poor, she
bought me three lunchboxes.
But when she went to fight,
the whole audience hated her.
They don't know anything.
Yeah, I'm with you on that one, brother.
Luffy, I'm sorry, but I don't
think I can follow Traffy's plan.
Whoa, Franky, where'd that come from?
Let me lay this out how I remember it.
We're supposed to destroy
the Smile Factory,
but then we keep Doflamingo
around to use against Kaido?
Aw, man.
It just ain't fair.
What happens to all the people who
want to take that bastard down?
We can't stop them anyway.
Even though this kingdom
seems like a happy place,
these guys know how dark it really is.
And right now,
they're getting ready to strike down
that darkness with all they've got,
even if it costs them their lives.
Sure, they're small, but they've
got some really big balls.
This little army is brave as hell,
staring down an enemy that's pure evil.
I can't just leave him to die.
I'm sorry.
It's not right to just
destroy the factory and bail.
As long as Doflamingo's in
charge, that's bad news.
Luffy, I think you're a
great captain and all, but...
I gotta fight!
Well, Franky...
He won't make it this time. He'll die.
Franky?
Kick some ass out there!
We'll back you up real soon!
Wow!
Thanks, brother!
All right.
We're heading back.
What?
It always ends up this way!
What's that?
Is the city under attack?
Isho, sir, there's a big
fight happening in the city.
We'd better hurry.
That was loud?
You got something going on over there?
This does not look promising.
It's coming this way!
What just happened?
I can't see You guys okay? What the?
Um, Vice Admiral Bastille?
Doflamingo!
Traffy!
Damn brat.
What's going on?
Traffy, why are you fighting with Mingo?
You just had to push your luck.
Cora, I...
Trophy!